ozeex.com 2011-05-14

# Welcome to RankRating.com, Rating System

## Privacy  Policies

At **RankRating.com** we realize that privacy is important to all of our customers. We utilize your personal information only to provide you with up to date reviews. This statement outlines how we care for your privacy. Therefore we do not lend, sell or rent mailing lists of our customers, so you never have to worry that your name, address, phone number and credit card information would ever be used outside of our business.  
RankRating.com uses Google AdSense and other third-party ad servers to serve and display advertisements on RankRating.com. These ad servers are not being provided any personally identifiable information by RankRating.com. They may use cookies, pixel trackers, content browsing, or other internet technology to improve the effectiveness and targeting of advertisements to you within RankRating.com and any other place where that third-party is serving advertisements. You may configure your web-browser to disable this. **                                                                **  
**IP address**

We may use your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help diagnose problems with our server and track movement within our web site only to optimize your experience. We may also collect the referring URL, access times and browser type. We will not link this information to any personally identifiable information.

**Cookies and Web beacons**

We may use, and may allow third parties to use, cookies and Web beacons on the Site and Review Service to monitor the effectiveness of advertising or for other legitimate purposes. These companies may use information about your visits to the Site and Review Service (not including your name, address or other personal information) to provide advertisements on the Site and Review Service, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  
Web beacons, also known as "Web bugs," are small, graphic images on Web pages or Web-based documents or in email messages that allow us or third parties to monitor who is visiting the Site or Review Service. Web beacons collect the IP address of the computer that the Web beacon is sent to, the URL of the page the Web beacon comes from and the time it was viewed. Web beacons may be linked to your personal information.

**Security**  
RankRating.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, perfect security does not exist on the Internet. Also, in theory third parties can intercept Internet transmissions containing your personal data, and we don't control the privacy/security of transmissions to and from the site while in transit. 

We also use third party advertisements on RankRating.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added

**Notifications**  
If we change our privacy policy, we will post a notice on our site so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their previously submitted information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**                                 **  
**Using Collected Information**  
We use the information we collect to:  
-contact you for administrative purposes or provide you with customer service;  
-complete transactions requested by you or to verify that you have submitted a review   to our Review Service;  
-respond to any questions, problems or complaints, or request feedback;  
-organize the Site and Review Service to better serve you and customize or develop our products and services; and  
-send you emails containing information about products and services that you might find of interest.  
-to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activity that threatens the network or otherwise violates the Usage Agreement;  
Personal information provided on our Site or through the Review Service may be linked together or merged with other personal information we obtain about you so that we may better understand your needs and inform you about our products or services and those of our business partners.   
**                                            **  
**Disclosure**  
We do not rent, sell or disclose personal information to third parties without your prior consent, except as described in this privacy policy. We may share personal information when we have your consent to do so, when required by law, when required to protect our rights or property, as necessary to complete a transaction you have requested, or for marketing purposes. We reserve the right to use and disclose any non-personal information that we collect. We may use third party service providers to assist us with the administration of the Site or Review Service or to perform other services for us, including transaction processing and sending email. These third parties may be given or may have access to your personal information, but agree to receive and use such information solely to provide services to us or on our behalf.   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, you may send us by mail at [rankrating@gmail.com](mailto:rankrating@gmail.com).
